Slow down.
You're gonna
make yourself sick.
You know...
we're sitting on
seven million bucks here.
Literally.
And?
I say we take it,
split it fifty-fifty,
take off.
It's not ours.
Could be.
Yeah, well, I know some people
who would have
a problem with that.
Them?
Don't worry about them.
You feeling right?
First thing we do,
take six million bucks
and build a time machine.
Those people that
you're worried about?
They'll never find us.
Where would you go first, huh?
- You-- You look like a history buff, right?
- Hm.
What, would you go
to Civil War times or...
Um, Ancient Rome?
Oh, Christ.
Mm. Hmm.
December 8, 2001.
Why?
No. No.
March 17, 1984.
Day I took my first bribe.
And then I'd go forward.
There's some people I'd like to
check on in five or ten years,
make sure they're doing okay.
You?
It's easy.
May 10, 1965.
That's the day Warren Buffett
took over
at Berkshire Hathaway.
I figure, got a million left
from building the time machine,
so I'd take my half
and just stick it
into Berkshire.
Then I'd come back here and...
I'm a billionaire.
Ohh.
Is there such a thing
as a trillionaire?
That's it. Money?
What else?
Nothing you'd change?
I'm rested.
-
Marion?
Are you still there?
Yes! It's a--
It's a little car.
Beige. I-- I--
I don't know the make.
Sixty-four, P...
...F, T, six.
He's headed south,
towards Curtis.
Oh, please get him.
12-14 responding.
On that 10-29, V as in Victor.
That's a Saturn Aura?
That is correct.
Saturn Aura, Nebraska
six-four-Paul-Frank-Tom-six.
White male, late 40s,
about 5'11", 180 pounds.
"Hoover Max Extract
Pressure-Pro, model sixty."
Hoover Pressure-Pro
Max Extract, model sixty.
-
- Ohh!
Anybody home?
Hands. Now.
I was at a party,
just minding my own business.
You are under arrest.
I better call Saul!
Hi. I'm Saul Goodman.
Did you know
that you have rights?
The Constitution says you do,
and so do I.
I believe that,
until proven guilty,
every man, woman, and child
in this country is innocent.
And that's why I fight for you,
Albuquerque! Better Call--
Hello, Krista? It's Gene.
Uh, uh, sorry
I wasn't in this morning.
Did you open up okay?
I'm fine.
C-Could you do me a favor?
The week's rotation
needs to be posted by 3:00.
Could you handle that?
Uh, one more thing. Um...
Just call the main office.
The-- The number
is on the bulletin board.
And, uh, let them know, um...
you're gonna need
a new manager.
This is how they get you?
This is how
they get you?
This is how they get you?
This is how
they get you?
Jesus.
What were you thinking?
What... were...
you... thinking?
Ow!
Shit!
Ah! Ah! Hey!
-
- Ahh!
I need another phone call!
-
- Another phone call!
William Oakley and Associates,
"Trust experience,
trust Oakley."
Bill Oakley speaking.
"Trust experience,
trust Oakley."
I like that. It's catchy.
You know who this is, right?
Saul?
You got it, buddy.
Wh-Wh-Wh-What are you, uh--
What-- What are y--
Uh, wha--
Uh, what are you doing?
Uh, you know I'm gonna
have to report this call.
Whoa. Calm down, Junior.
The cops know
all about the call.
They're probably listening in.
The fact is,
I'm standing in the middle
of a police station
as we speak.
So they finally caught you.
Listen. This is your lucky day.
I am talking to Saul Goodman's
new advisory counsel.
What?
Keep up, Bill.
You hit the jackpot.
"Advisory counsel?"
This puts you
on the map, amigo.
Here's what you're gonna do.
You're gonna grab a flight
to Omaha, Nebraska, ASAP.
There's nothing direct,
so you're gonna have to
connect through Houston.
Wh-- Who's paying for this?
- You are. Listen. You hear that?
- Hear what?
Bang, bang!
That's opportunity knocking.
Get off your ass
and answer the door.
Okay, on your way
to the airport...
- Wait. Wait. Hold on.
- ...I need you to make some calls.
Even supposing, hypothetically,
I'd be willing
to take this on--
"Willing"?
Bill, this is a career-maker.
Get real. You're doing this.
The DA has a warehouse
of evidence against you--
I can't even begin to imagine
what the Feds are sitting on.
No matter who your lawyer is,
you are screwed.
So I've gotta ask...
Where do you see this ending?
Where do I see it ending? Um...
RICO.
Not five, not ten,
but twenty-seven
predicate violations.
Federal conspiracy
to manufacture and distribute
a controlled substance.
On this scale?
Life sentence, stat max.
Money laundering.
Eight counts, 20 years each.
One hundred sixty years,
stat max.
We'll argue for
consecutive sentencing.
Accessory
after the fact
to multiple murders.
Including two decorated
federal officers.
Fifteen years each.
By our count,
that's life plus...
One hundred ninety.
Life plus 190 years.
All right.
I'm willing to extend
a one-time,
take-it-or-leave-it offer.
Here's the headline: 30 years.
Keep your nose clean,
stay healthy,
you have a shot at seeing
daylight in your old age.
Mr. Oakley, your "co-counsel,"
is he here with us?
Uh, listen, you've got
Agent Schrader's widow
back there.
- Why don't you invite her in?
- Uh, wait a sec--
I mean, you owe her
that much, don't you?
Well, no, she--
she can't be present at a--
a plea negotiation.
It's completely inappropriate.
She's already here.
Both parties agree.
It's fine. Really.
They tell me they found you
in a garbage dumpster.
Well, that makes sense.
My husband was the best man
that I have ever known.
He lived to help others.
If somebody was in trouble,
no matter the time,
no matter the place,
Hank Schrader would be there.
With a smile and a joke.
He was kind,
he was decent,
he was strong.
His partner...
Steve Gomez.
Steve and Blanca
made a home that was warm
and full of laughter.
Three children.
Three fatherless children.
Hank and Steve, the good guys.
They were shot dead
and left in a hole
in the desert.
And you.
You helped
the two-faced
poisonous bastard
behind it all.
For what?
Money.
You did it all for money.
No matter
what they do with you now,
no matter where they put you
or for how long,
it will never be enough.
Mrs... Mrs. Schrader.
The loss
that you've suffered...
It's unspeakable.
I met your husband a few times.
He was a man
who stood by his word
and was very good at his job.
A straight shooter.
You and he are...
victims.
And so am I.
Two years ago
a man came into my office.
He said his name was Mayhew.
He wanted one of my clients
to lie under oath.
He offered me money.
I declined.
Any lawyer would.
That night, as I was leaving
my office, I was attacked.
Two men
threw a sack over my head,
they hogtied me,
and they drove me
out into the desert.
And when they pulled
the hood off,
I was kneeling
in front of an open grave.
With a gun pointed at my head.
That was my introduction
to Walter White.
From that moment on,
there hasn't been a minute
that I wasn't afraid.
Yeah. I worked for him.
I made a lot of money.
But that's not why I did it.
I did it because
I knew what he would do
to me if I refused.
Over and over, I thought
about going to the police.
I even thought about
talking to Agent Schrader.
But I knew that Walter White
would kill me, wherever I was.
And I was right.
You look it up.
October 4, 2009.
They murdered ten men
inside three prisons
in the space of two minutes.
Knifed.
Throats slashed.
A man was burned alive.
They even killed
one of my colleagues, a lawyer.
He was cooperating
with the DEA.
Daniel Wachsburger.
The news said
Dan was stabbed 48 times.
So, yeah,
when it all blew up, I ran.
But not from the police.
From them.
Walter White might be dead,
but Jesse Pinkman
and the others?
They're still out there, somewhere.
Mrs. Schrader...
you are looking at a man
who has lost everything.
My profession.
My family. My freedom.
I have-- I have nobody.
I have nothing.
And you think
jurors are gonna buy that?
One.
All I need is one.
Oakley tells me that
you've never lost a case.
Is that so?
That's a hell of a record.
You should be proud of that.
Still...
Juries, right?
Whew. You never can tell.
It's a roll of the dice.
I'm just-- I'm hoping
there's some wiggle room.
You are not going to
negotiate with this man.
You're not.
Seventeen.
After sentence has been imposed
on the counts
to which
defendant pleads guilty
as agreed herein,
the government
will move to dismiss
Counts Three through Nine
of the indictment.
Eighteen.
Based on the facts
now known to the government,
the anticipated
offense level is 35,
which, when combined
with the anticipated criminal
history category of 1,
results in an anticipated
advisory sentencing
guidelines range
of 85 to 90 months imprisonment,
in addition
to any supervised release,
fine, and restitution
the Court may impose.
Seven and a half years.
Let's get
this thing signed
and get the hell out of here.
We're good with that.
"Nineteen."
"Term to be served at
FCI Butner Low, North Carolina,
Wing D."
FCI Butner Low.
It's a great location.
Very nice weather.
It's the only
federal institution
with a golf program.
It was good enough
for Bernie Madoff...
This is an actual request?
Are you kidding?
I give you guys half a chance,
you're gonna throw me into
gen pop in some hellhole.
I visited a client once
at ADX Montrose.
"The Alcatraz of the Rockies."
No. No, that's a dealbreaker,
my friend.
FCI Butner Low. Wing...
D. Wing D.
-
- "Wing D."
And now we are done.
Ah, as Steve Jobs used to say,
one more thing.
"Twenty."
"During incarceration,
Defendant Goodman to receive
one pint Blue Bell
mint chocolate chip ice cream
every Friday for the duration."
Are you kidding?
He's kidding.
"Blue Bell
Mint Chocolate Chip."
No substitutions.
Okay. That's it.
Hold on.
I can oil everybody's locks.
- No more games.
- No. I got a sweetener.
It's nothing I've talked about.
New arena. Primo stuff.
Go.
Inside story,
previously unknown
felony homicide.
It concerns a prominent
Albuquerque attorney
who, uh, disappeared,
believed to have
killed himself.
Howard Hamlin?
You're talking
about Howard Hamlin.
That's your "sweetener"?
He's trying to sell us
the Hamlin thing.
He thought
he really had something.
Sounds like you and your ex
aren't talking
on a regular basis.
Kim Wexler walked into
the Albuquerque DA's office
last month.
She spilled her guts about
Howard Hamlin, on the record.
You got
nothing left to sell.
Last chance.
Do we go to trial,
or do we have a deal?
Yes!
Yes, we have a deal.
-
Ugh. Of course.
Am I gonna be sorry
if I ask what's going on?
I'm putting a stop to it.
A stop to what?
-
- To what?
Listen. Just-- No. Just listen.
That click?
The click.
The flame is lighting
and then it keeps going out.
So it's either
a thermocouple that's corroded
or we have a short.
A thermocouple is corroded.
Okay. I got it.
Hey, uh, maybe we could
just unplug it?
- Or cut a wire or something?
- No. Listen.
I see no reason
to stay down here
without hot water
when it's something
that I can easily fix.
Aha!
I think this will do the trick.
You wouldn't happen to have
a pocket knife or a screwdriver
in one of those bags,
would you?
No.
What? Speak up!
-
Come on!
- There we go.
Yeah. This should work.
-
Hey, you're a scientist, right?
So, uh, I have a question.
What would you do
if you had a time machine?
A time machine?
Yeah, um...
From a scientist's
point of view.
-
- You can go backwards, forwards.
Uh, where would you go?
A meaningless question.
Time--
A time machine.
Look, time travel,
the kind of time travel
that you're thinking of,
is a scientific impossibility.
It would violate the Second Law
of Thermodynamics.
- Uh, but what about a wormhole?
- Ohh!
Well, I was watching NOVA,
and Alan Alda seemed to think--
Oh, well, then Alan Alda,
he's the expert.
Oh, Christ. Are you kidding me?
Quantum mechanics?
We're discussing that now?
Stay in your lane.
It's just a thought experiment.
There's gotta be something
you'd go back and change
if you could.
Oh, you are not talking
about a time machine,
which is both a real
and theoretical impossibility.
You are talking about regrets.
So if you want to ask
about regrets,
just ask about regrets
and leave all this
time-traveling nonsense
out of it.
Okay. Regrets, then.
Regrets.
Yeah.
My regrets. All right, well...
My regrets...
Well...
-
When I was a graduate student,
I started a company
with some...
At the time, I thought
they were my friends.
Our goal was to
commercialize discoveries
that I had made.
And at a certain point...
I stepped away.
I thought I was doing
the gentlemanly thing.
But little did I understand
that they were
artfully maneuvering me
into leaving my own creation.
And had I stayed, oh...
Well...
I wouldn't be
down here with you.
So you started a company.
Is it still around?
Oh, yes.
Is it successful?
Very.
How could you never
tell me about this?
We could have
done something with this.
Wrongful termination,
intellectual property theft,
uh, patent fraud.
I mean, I coulda
sunk my teeth into this!
You'd have been the last lawyer
I'd have gone to.
- Yeah. Sure.
-
So, what about you?
- What?
- Regrets?
Y-- Wait. I got one.
You know what? Never mind.
When I was 20--
um, 22,
I pulled a slip and fall
outside Marshall Field's.
- Uh--
- I did.
And I was stupid and young
and I was trying to show off.
So I hit the ice
as fast as I could.
I biffed it so hard,
I heard a crack!
Whew.
Wasn't the ice, it was me.
I actually hurt myself.
I mean, I-- My knee
has never been the same.
"A slip and fall"?
Yeah. That's how I put myself
through bartending school.
-
- Right.
So...
So you were always like this.
Sorry.
Psst! Bill! Hey.
I'm just going to--
Sir, this man
is a federal prisoner.
I'm a US Marshal.
I ask you not to speak to him.
That's my lawyer.
Is that true?
You're his lawyer?
Yes.
You'll have other opportunities
to talk to your client.
Please move out of the aisle.
No, hold on.
N-Nothing I say in front of you
is privileged, right?
That's right.
So if I talk to my attorney
and we let something slip
that could help
the government's case,
you could pass it along
to the prosecution.
Totally clean.
Correct.
With that in mind, you're sure
we can't have a few words?
Make it fast.
She confessed.
What's the DA gonna do with it?
No witnesses,
no physical evidence.
If I had to guess,
most likely they sit on it.
Permanently.
Okay.
No, not "okay."
Not for her.
Her problem's not the DA.
What then?
Well, apparently, Kim took her
sworn and notarized statement
and hand delivered it
to Hamlin's widow.
- No.
- Yes.
She opened herself up
to a civil suit.
The widow can take her
for everything she has
and everything
she's gonna have,
in perpetuity.
So, is she? Suing?
Look, all I can tell you
for sure
is that Mrs. Hamlin's out
lawyer shopping as we speak.
Not that she bothered
to call me.
Hey, can I, uh,
go to the john now?
I'm going.
Hold up, Bill.
No, wait.
You're gonna love this.
The Hamlin thing?
The government
doesn't know the half of it.
As soon as we land,
I want you
to tell the other side
that I've got more
to trade, okay?
I j-just remembered something
that'll make their toes curl.
Okay.
Anything that makes
their "toes curl"
is bound to jam Kim up.
If it involves her.
Oh, it involves her.
Kim's already got a civil suit
hanging over her head.
You give the government more,
maybe they bring
the hammer down.
What more are you gonna get?
What's left?
You don't understand.
It's really good ice cream.
- Boys again?
- Girls this time.
Well, she's not sleeping
for a year or two.
- At least.
- Is she coming back?
She'll have to.
Josh is a twin, isn't he?
Oh, yeah. And it's
his birthday next week.
I always take him out,
just the two of us,
because, you know,
he had to share everything.
Well, that's nice.
It's either Red Lobster
or that new
Middle Eastern place,
the one over on Wickham.
- Top something?
- Topkapi.
That's it. Topkapi.
Glen took you there, didn't he?
What'd you guys think?
Uh, it wasn't...
Not good, huh?
No, uh... No. It was fine.
Would Josh like it?
He-- He might.
Okay. Another birthday
at Red Lobster.
He can live with that.
What did we
get them for the shower?
A stroller, right?
Yeah, one of the nice ones
with the shock absorbers.
With twins? They might need
a double stroller...
You, too, Donny.
Seana, Donny from
TPC Sawgrass, line four.
Hey, Tammy. I'm leaving early.
Can you let Ricardo know?
- Sure. No prob.
-
Thanks.
Palm Coast Sprinkler.
Watering your world since 1978.
If he shows up,
you keep that door locked.
You call the police,
and then you call me.
Any time, day or night.
Okay?
- Okay.
- I'll see you Thursday.
Let me know
if you need me to pick you up.
- All right. Thank you.
- Okay.
Ladies, it's right this way.
Sorry about the heat.
AC's on the fritz.
Fill this out.
And, before you ask,
there's no charge.
All our services are free.
Oh, a-actually, I'm here
to see if I can volunteer.
You want to volunteer?
- Yes.
-
Can you answer a phone?
Sure.
Then there you go.
Central Florida Legal Aid.
How can I help you?
- Hello?
- Kim?
- Yes. - This is Suzanne Ericsen.
Hi, Suzanne.
I want to make it clear
this call
is completely unofficial.
All right.
I shouldn't even
be talking to you.
But considering everything,
I think it's only right
you know what's going on.
You've seen the news?
I don't think so.
Your ex, "Saul Goodman"?
He was arrested in Nebraska.
He's been extradited
to New Mexico.
When was this?
Two days ago.
But that's not why I'm calling.
He's giving testimony
that affects you, personally.
What kind of testimony?
♪ Only believe ♪
♪ My Lordy ♪
♪ All things ♪
♪ Are possible ♪
♪ If you'll only ♪
♪ Believe ♪
♪ Lordy ♪
♪ Only believe ♪
-** Yeah ** -** My Lordy ♪
♪ Ohh ♪
♪ All things are possible ♪
♪ If you only ♪
♪ Believe ♪
It's showtime.
All rise
for the right honorable
Judge Samantha Small.
Court's now in session.
Please take a seat.
Okay, item one on the calendar,
CR 10-7253 United States
of America versus...
Defendant has requested
to use the name Saul Goodman.
So it's "United States
versus Saul Goodman."
Counsel, please state
your appearances.
AUSA George Castellano.
With me is Elizabeth Nooryani,
Trial Attorney from the
Drug Enforcement Section
of the Department of Justice,
AUSAs Sarah Braddock,
Neel Patel, and Hillary Park
and Special Agent in Charge
Austin Ramey from the DEA.
Also present in the courtroom,
Zachary Hernandez,
Special Agent in Charge
of the FBI in New Mexico.
Your Honor, I'd also
like to note the presence
of the victims
who are here this morning,
Marie Schrader
and Blanca Gomez.
William Oakley
appearing as advisory counsel.
Saul Goodman appearing
on his own behalf.
Good morning.
The defendant still wants
to represent himself?
Uh... That's right, your Honor.
Okay.
The parties have reached
a plea agreement
satisfactory to both sides.
However, I have reviewed
the government's
sentencing recommendations
and...
well, I have questions.
Mr. Castellano, will you please
come up to the microphone?
Mr. Castellano,
today we consider the sentence
for a defendant
who will be pleading guilty
to multiple felonies,
RICO offenses,
money laundering, conspiracy,
accessory after the fact
to the murder
of federal officers.
And for these offenses,
the government's sentencing
recommendation is seven years.
Your Honor,
I can assure you
my colleagues and I
gave every aspect
of this recommendation
careful consideration.
Help me understand.
Has the defendant provided
substantial assistance
to the government?
Your Honor?
Mr. Oakley,
please advise your client
to stay silent at this time.
Your Honor, with respect,
Mr. Oakley is advisory counsel.
I'm representing myself
here today.
If I may say something that
I think will help the court
fully understand the situation?
Mr. Goodman,
you are the beneficiary
of the most generous
sentencing recommendation
I've seen in 22 years
on the bench.
Any statement you make
imperils that recommendation.
I'm very aware of that,
Your Honor.
Uh, if you'll
allow me to speak,
I-- I think I can save
the court's valuable time.
Go ahead.
Briefly.
Two years ago
a man came into my office.
He said his name was Mayhew.
He wanted one of my clients
to lie for him under oath.
He offered me money. I refused.
That night, as I was leaving
my office, I was attacked.
A bag was shoved over my head,
I was hogtied,
I was driven
out into the desert.
And when they pulled
the hood off,
I was kneeling
in front of an open grave
with a gun pointed at my head.
That was my introduction
to Walter White!
I was terrified.
But not for long.
That night, I saw opportunity.
A shot at big money.
And I grabbed it
and I held it tight.
And for the next 16 months,
my every waking moment
was spent building
Walter White's drug empire.
Hold on, Mr. Goodman.
Stop right there.
Consult Mr. Oakley
before you say another word.
Your Honor, I believe the court
deserves the whole truth.
You are contradicting
your plea agreement's
sworn factual basis.
No offense, Your Honor, but I--
I think I know the law here
better than you do.
Your Honor,
we'd like to request a recess.
No, we do not need a recess.
Your Honor, we are satisfied
for Mr. Goodman to continue.
Your Honor,
I'd like to petition
to withdraw from this case.
- Denied.
- Respectfully--
Not a chance.
Bobbi, swear Mr. Goodman in.
Do you swear that the evidence
you shall give to the court
in this matter
shall be the truth,
the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth
so help you God?
I do.
Mr. Goodman,
you are now under oath.
Any false statement you make
can be used in prosecution
for perjury
or obstruction of justice.
Do you understand?
- Yes.
- All right.
In the last 24 hours,
have you used
any alcohol or other drugs?
No, Your Honor.
Are you taking
any prescription medications?
No.
All right.
Continue.
Oh, um,
I lied to the government
about, uh, Kim Wexler.
Uh, I fed them a load of BS
about her involvement
in Howard Hamlin's murder.
I just-- I just wanted her
to come here today.
I wanted her to hear this.
So, yeah, I wasn't there
when the meth was cooked.
I wasn't there
when it was sold.
I didn't witness
any of the murders,
but I damn well knew
it was happening.
I was more than
a willing participant.
I was indispensable.
I kept Walter White
out of jail,
I laundered his money,
I lied for him,
I conspired with him,
and I made millions.
If he hadn't walked
into my office that day,
Walter White
would have been dead
or behind bars within a month.
And Agent Schrader
and Agent Gomez
and a whole lot of other people
would still be alive.
Fact is, Walter White
couldn't have
done it without me.
You got that?
Your Honor, we move to
strike Mr. Goodman's comments.
On what grounds?
- Um, speculation.
- Speculation?
He's testifying
to his own actions.
Your Honor, uh,
he's describing events
that would have transpired
had he acted differently.
I have one more thing to say.
- Sit down, Mr. Goodman. Now.
- Please, your Honor. Please.
The government urges the court
to allow Mr. Goodman
to continue.
How is that
not speculation?
All right, Mr. Goodman.
Go ahead.
What happened
to Howard Hamlin was...
it was...
I can't even...
After that,
Kim had the guts to start over.
She left town, but...
I'm the one who ran away.
And my brother Chuck--
Uh, Charles McGill.
Y-You may have known him.
He was
an incredible lawyer, as--
The most brilliant guy
I ever met.
But he was limited.
I tried.
I could have tried harder.
I should have.
- Instead, when--
- Your Honor.
Bill, please.
Just let me get through this.
Instead, when I saw a chance
to hurt him, I took it.
I got his malpractice insurance canceled.
I took away
the one thing he lived for,
the law.
After that, he killed himself.
And I'll live with that.
What was all that?
That thing with your brother,
that wasn't even a crime.
Yeah, it was.
Mr. Goodman,
sit down and stay seated.
The name's McGill.
I'm James McGill.
Your Honor,
in view of the defendant's
confession...
We'd like
to request a recess--
- ...the Government withdraws its sentencing recommendation.
- Hold on.
- That was not a confession.
- And urges this court
to impose the statutory maximum
for each of these offenses.
That was not a confession.
It was merely, uh,
a single point of view...
Furthermore, your Honor,
a second additional hearing
is required...
...in a very complex,
uh, narrative...
...to assess
the additional claims
Mr. Goodman--
I'm sorry-- Mr. McGill
has now admitted to,
Did you ground yourself?
Yes, I did!
-
- Oh, crap!
I was starting to worry.
My car conked out on the 40.
I almost got creamed
by a cement truck.
Oh, um,
they had those apples
that you like.
I got you half a dozen Fuji.
Um, and the newsstand
on Central
said they might start carrying
the Financial Times.
So that's good, right?
What?
You know I could
hire someone to do this.
I could get someone
from the office.
I'm doing it.
Yeah, every day?
While you're trying
to start a...practice?
Why?
'Cause you're my brother.
Duh.
You'd do the same for me.
Mm. Well,
you could stay for a while.
We could talk.
Talk? What about?
Well, your cases. Your clients.
You want to talk
about my clients?
Seriously?
You want to talk about,
uh, the granny who got
picked up for soliciting
inside a Christian Science
Reading Room?
Wh-- What about the kid
who broke into a liquor store
and drank five bottles
of creme de menthe
and then passed out
behind the counter?
They deserve
a vigorous defense.
Like any other client.
Or maybe you just wanna tell me
what I'm doing wrong.
That's not what I had in mind.
I'm hoping you didn't steal
that from a motel ice machine.
You can hope.
I'm gonna take a pass
on the heart-to-heart, Chuck.
One of my "deserving" clients,
he got caught waving the weenie
outside a Hobby Lobby.
Hold on.
You got to reimburse yourself.
Mm. This one's on me.
Jimmy...
If you don't like
where you're heading,
there's no shame in going back
and changing your path.
Uh, when have you ever
"changed your path"?
Hey. Think on it.
We always end up
having the same conversation,
don't we?
I'll see ya tomorrow, Chuck.
And I might have
the Financial Times.
I know you?
Hey.
"Better Call Saul."
Right?
McGill.
What?
I'm McGill.
Don't give me that.
You're Saul!
It's Better Call Saul.
No shit.
Psst! Psst!
Back here, yo.
Back here.
See? Toldja!
It's Better Call Saul!
You're right. Better Call Saul.
Hi.
Yeah. Better Call Saul.
- Better...
-
- Call...
Saul.
- Better...
-
- Call...
Saul.
Better Call Saul!
- All of you, shut up!
- Better Call Saul!
- I said shut up!
- Shut the hell up!
- Better Call Saul!
-
Better Call...
Saul! Lawyer's here!
I got ya, Saul.
- Ma'am?
- No cuffs, please.
Thank you.
Hi, Jimmy.
Hi.
How did you...
Uh, turns out
my New Mexico bar card
doesn't have
an expiration date.
You had them down
to seven years.
Yeah, I did.
Eighty-six years.
But with good behavior...
who knows?
Here we go, here we go.
慢点
你会的
你知道的。。。
我们坐在上面
字面上
和
我说我们接受它，
一半一半，
起飞
这不是我们的。
可以是。
是的，我认识一些人
谁会呢
他们
别担心他们。
你感觉对吗？
我们做的第一件事，
拿六百万美元
那些
他们永远找不到我们。
你会先去哪里？
-你看起来像个历史迷，对吧？
什么，你会去吗
嗯，古罗马？
哦，天哪。
二○○一年十二月八日。
为什么？
不，不。
1984年3月17日。
我第一次受贿的那天。
然后我会继续前进。
有些人我想去
确保他们做得很好。
你
这很容易。
1965年5月10日。
这就是沃伦·巴菲特的日子
接管
我想，还剩一百万
所以我会拿我的那一半
坚持下去
然后我会回到这里。。。
我是个亿万富翁。
有这样的事吗
就这样。钱
还有什么？
没什么你会改变的？
我休息了。
马里恩
对这是一场比赛--
米色。我--
六十四，P。。。
…F，T，六。
他向南走，
哦，请把他找来。
12-14响应。
在那10-29，V代表维克多。
那是土星光环
没错。
土星光环，内布拉斯加州
白人男性，40多岁，
“胡佛马克斯提取物
胡佛压力专业
有人在家吗？
手。现在
我参加了一个聚会，
只管自己的事。
你被捕了。
我最好叫索尔
嗨。我是索尔·古德曼。
你知道吗
宪法上说你会的
我相信，
每个男人、女人和孩子
这就是我为你而战的原因，
你好，克丽斯塔？是基恩。
呃，呃，对不起
你开门了吗？
我很好。
本周轮换
你能处理吗？
嗯，还有一件事。嗯。。。
打电话给总公司就行了。
数字
然后，呃，让他们知道，嗯。。。
你会需要的
他们就是这样抓到你的？
这是怎么回事
上帝啊
你在想什么？
什么…我们。。。
倒霉！
啊!！啊!！嘿
我需要另一个电话！
威廉·奥克利及其同事，
“信任经验，
我是比尔·奥克利。
“信任体验，
我喜欢这样。它很吸引人。
你知道这是谁，对吧
索尔？
你明白了，伙计。
你是什么--
嗯，什么--
呃，你知道我会的
哇。冷静点，孩子。
警察知道
他们可能在监听。
事实是，
警察局的
所以他们终于抓住你了。
听着。今天是你的幸运日。
我正在和索尔·古德曼的通话
什么
继续，比尔。
“咨询顾问？”
这让你
这是你要做的。
你要搭飞机吗
没有直接的，
所以你必须这样做
谁来付钱？
-你是。听着 你听到了吗
砰，砰！
滚开
好的，在路上
-等等。等待等一下。
即使假设，
我愿意
“愿意”
现实一点。你正在这样做。
地方检察官有一个仓库
我甚至无法想象
无论你的律师是谁，
所以我得问问…
你在哪里看到这个结局
我在哪里看到它的结局？嗯。。。
里科。
不是五个，不是十个。
但是二十七
联邦阴谋
受控物质。
在这种规模上？
洗钱
八次，每次20年。
一百六十年，
我们会为你辩护的
附件
包括两个装饰件
每人15年。
根据我们的统计，
一百九十。
生命加上190年。
好吧
一次性，
标题是：30年。
保持你的鼻子干净，
你有机会看看
奥克利先生，你的“协理律师”
他和我们在一起吗？
呃，听着，你有
-你为什么不邀请她进来？
我是说，你欠她的
哦，不，她--
认罪谈判。
她已经来了。
双方同意。
他们告诉我他们找到你了
嗯，这是有道理的。
我丈夫是伴郎
他活着是为了帮助别人。
如果有人遇到麻烦，
无论在什么地方，
带着微笑和玩笑。
他很善良，
他很正派，
他很强壮。
他的搭档。。。
史蒂夫·戈麦斯。
史蒂夫和布兰卡
建造了一个温暖的家
三个孩子。
三个没有父亲的孩子。
汉克和史蒂夫，好人。
他们被枪杀了
然后留在洞里
和你。
你帮助了我
两面派
为了什么？
钱
你这么做都是为了钱。
不管怎样
不管他们把你放在哪里
这永远不够。
施拉德夫人。
损失
这是无法形容的。
我见过你丈夫几次。
他是个男人
他的工作非常出色。
直截了当的人。
你和他是。。。
受害者。
我也是。
两年前
他说他的名字叫梅休。
他想要我的一个客户
他给了我钱。
我拒绝了。
任何律师都会。
那天晚上，我正要离开
两个人
他们大嚼我，
他们开车送我
当他们拉动时
我跪着
用枪指着我的头。
这是我的介绍
从那一刻起，
一分钟也没有
是 啊我为他工作。
但这不是我做这件事的原因。
我这样做是因为
一遍又一遍，我想
我甚至想过
但我知道沃尔特·怀特
我是对的。
你查一下。
2009年10月4日。
他们杀了十个人
在两分钟的时间内。
被刺伤。
喉咙被割伤。
一名男子被活活烧死。
他们甚至被杀了
他在合作
丹尼尔·沃克斯伯格。
消息说
所以，是的，
但不是来自警方。
从他们那里。
沃尔特·怀特可能已经死了，
但是杰西·平克曼
他们还在外面的某个地方。
施拉德夫人。。。
你在看一个男人
这是我的职业。
我一个人也没有。
我什么都没有。
你觉得呢
一
我只需要一个。
奥克利告诉我的
是这样吗？
这是一个地狱般的记录。
还
陪审团，对吧？
呼。你永远不知道。
这是一个掷骰子的游戏。
我只是希望
你不会去的
你不是。
十七
在判刑之后
到
政府
数到三到九
十八
根据事实
预期的
当组合时
对于预期的罪犯
结果得到预期的结果
咨询判决
监禁85至90个月，
此外
罚款和赔偿
七年半。
让我们开始吧
然后离开这里。
我们对此很在行。
“十九岁。”
“在下列地点送达的期限：
D翼。“
FCI Butner低。
这是个好地方。
这是唯一的选择
这已经足够好了
这是真正的请求吗？
你在开玩笑吗？
我给你们半个机会，
你要把我扔进监狱吗
我拜访过一位客户
“落基山脉的恶魔岛”
不，不，那是个破坏交易的人，
FCI Butner低。翼
D、 翼D。
现在我们完成了。
啊，就像史蒂夫·乔布斯常说的，
“二十。”
“在监禁期间，
一品脱蓝色铃铛
在此期间，每周五。”
你在开玩笑吗？
他在开玩笑。
“蓝铃
没有替代品。
可以就这样。
等等
-别再玩游戏了。
这不是我说过的。
这是一个新的舞台。这是一种原始的东西。
去
内部故事，
前所未闻
它涉及一个突出的问题
谁，呃，失踪了，
据信有
霍华德·哈姆林？
你在说话
那是你的“甜味剂”？
他想出卖我们
他想
听起来像你和你的前任
你不说话吗
金·韦克斯勒走进房间
她大发雷霆
你有
这是最后一次机会。
我们要去审判吗，
对
是的，我们有协议。
啊。当然
我会后悔吗
我要阻止它。
停下来干什么？
听不，听我说。
那个咔哒声？
点击。
火焰正在燃烧
然后它就一直出去。
所以要么
或者我们有一个短。
热电偶被腐蚀。
嘿，呃，也许我们可以
-或者割断电线什么的？
我看没有理由
当它的东西
啊哈！
我想这会成功的。
你不会碰巧有
在其中一个袋子中，
不
什么说话！
来吧
是 啊这应该行得通。
嘿，你是科学家，对吧？
所以，呃，我有个问题。
你会怎么做
时间机器？
是的，嗯。。。
来自科学家的
呃，你要去哪里？
一个毫无意义的问题。
时间--
时间机器。
看，时间旅行，
这种时间旅行
这在科学上是不可能的。
这将违反第二定律
-那虫洞呢？
嗯，我在看＜I＞新星＜/I＞节目
哦，那么艾伦·阿尔达，
哦，天哪。你在开玩笑吧？
量子力学？
留在你的车道上。
这只是一个思想实验。
一定有什么事
如果可以的话。
哦，你没说话
这两者都是真实的
你说的是遗憾。
所以如果你想问
问问后悔的事就行了
然后离开这一切
可以遗憾，那么。
遗憾。
是 啊
这是我的遗憾。好吧，好吧。。。
我的遗憾。。。
好
当我还是研究生的时候，
我开了一家公司
当时，我想
我们的目标是
在某一点上。。。
我走开了。
我以为我在做
但我一点也不明白
他们是
离开我自己的创作。
如果我留下来，哦。。。
好
我不会的
所以你开了一家公司。
哦，是的。
它成功了吗？
非常
你怎么可能永远不会呢
我们本来可以的
错误终止，
呃，专利欺诈。
我是说，我可以
你会是最后一个律师
-嗯。当然
那你呢？
-什么？
等等。我有一个。
你知道吗？不要介意。
我20岁的时候--
嗯,22,，
我滑倒了
我又笨又年轻
所以我撞到冰上了
我狠狠地咬了它，
呼。
我真的伤到自己了。
我是说，我的膝盖
“滑倒”？
是 啊我就是这么说的
所以
所以你总是这样。
很抱歉
嘘！账单嘿
我正要去--
先生，这个人
我是美国元帅。
我请你不要和他说话。
那是我的律师。
这是真的吗？
对
你还有其他机会
请离开走道。
不，等等。
我在你面前没说什么
这是正确的。
所以如果我和我的律师谈谈
这可能会有帮助
你可以把它传下去
完全干净。
对的
考虑到这一点，你确定吗
快点。
她承认了。
没有证人，
如果让我猜的话，
永久地
可以
不，不是“好的”
不适合她。
然后呢？
显然，金姆带走了她
并亲手交付
-不。
她敞开心扉
寡妇可以带走她
还有一切
那么，她是谁？起诉？
听着，我只能告诉你
是哈姆林太太出去了吗
并不是说她烦恼
嘿，我能，呃，
我要走了。
等等，比尔。
不，等等。
哈姆林事件？
我们一着陆，
我想要你
我还有更多
我刚刚想起一件事
那会让他们的脚趾弯曲。
可以
任何能使
肯定会把金弄得一团糟。
如果涉及到她。
哦，这涉及到她。
金已经有民事诉讼了
你给政府更多，
也许他们会带来
你还能得到什么？
还剩下什么？
你不明白。
这真是一个很好的冰淇淋。
-又是男孩？
她没睡
-至少。
她不得不这么做。
乔希是双胞胎，不是吗？
哦，是的。而且它是
我总是带他出去，
因为，你知道，
嗯，那很好。
要么是红龙虾
还是那个新的
-在什么上面？
就这样。托普卡比。
格伦带你去的，不是吗？
呃，不是。。。
不好吧？
不，不，没事。
乔希喜欢吗？
他，他可能。
可以又一个生日
他可以接受。
我们做了什么
是的，一个不错的
双胞胎？他们可能需要
你也是，唐尼。
西娜，唐尼
嘿，塔米。我要早点走。
-当然。没问题。
谢谢
棕榈海岸洒水车。
从1978年开始为你的世界浇水。
如果他出现，
你报警，
任何时间，白天或晚上。
可以
-好的。
让我知道
-好的。非常感谢。
女士们，这边走。
对不起，太热了。
填好这个。
我们所有的服务都是免费的。
哦，事实上，我在这儿
你想当志愿者吗？
-对。
你能接电话吗？
当然
那你就去吧。
佛罗里达州中部法律援助中心。
-喂？
-对 -我是苏珊娜·埃里克森。
嗨，苏珊娜。
我想说清楚
这个电话
好的。
我甚至不应该
但考虑到一切，
我认为这是完全正确的
你看过新闻了吗
我不这么认为。
你的前任，索尔·古德曼
他在内布拉斯加州被捕。
他已被引渡
这是什么时候？
两天前。
但这不是我打电话的原因。
他在作证
什么样的证词？
♪ 只相信♪
♪ 大人♪
♪ 万事♪
♪ 是可能的♪
♪ 如果你愿意的话♪
♪ 相信♪
♪ 老爷♪
♪ 只相信♪
-**是的**-**大人♪
♪ 哦♪
♪ 一切皆有可能♪
♪ 如果你只是♪
♪ 相信♪
表演时间到了。
全体起立
法庭现在开庭。
好的日历上的第一项，
美国CR 10-7253
被告要求：
所以它是美国
律师，请陈述
奥萨·乔治·卡斯特拉诺。
和我在一起的是伊丽莎白·努里亚尼，
法院的审判律师
AUSAs Sarah Braddock，
还有负责的特工
也出现在法庭上，
扎卡里·埃尔南德斯，
新墨西哥州的联邦调查局。
法官大人，我也希望
今天早上谁在这里，
玛丽·施拉德
威廉·奥克利
索尔·古德曼出现了
早上好
被告仍然想要
嗯……没错，法官大人。
可以
双方已达成协议
双方都满意。
然而，我已经回顾了
政府的
和
嗯，我有问题。
卡斯特拉诺先生，请你
卡斯特拉诺先生，
对于被告
对于多起重罪，
洗钱、阴谋，
事后从犯
谋杀案
对于这些罪行，
政府的判决
法官大人，
我可以向你保证
给每个方面
仔细考虑。
帮我理解。
被告是否提供：
法官大人？
奥克利先生，
在这个时候保持沉默。
法官大人，恕我直言，
我代表我自己
请允许我说点什么
完全了解情况？
古德曼先生，
最慷慨的
我已经看了22年了
你有什么声明吗
我很清楚这一点，
呃，如果你愿意的话
我想我能救你
着手
短暂地
两年前
他说他的名字叫梅休。
他想要我的一个客户
他给了我钱。我拒绝了。
那天晚上，我正要离开
一个袋子被推到我头上，
我被困住了，
我被驱使着
当他们拉动时
我跪着
用枪指着我的头。
这是我的介绍
我吓坏了。
但不会太久。
那天晚上，我看到了机会。
一笔巨款。
我抓住了它
在接下来的16个月里，
我醒着的每一刻
等等，古德曼先生。
咨询奥克利先生
法官大人我相信法庭
你在自相矛盾
无意冒犯法官大人但我--
我想我知道这里的法律
法官大人，
不，我们不需要休息。
法官大人我们很满意
法官大人，
我想请愿
-否认。
不可能。
鲍比，向古德曼先生发誓。
你发誓证据确凿吗
你应向法庭提出上诉
将是真理，
只有真相
我愿意。
古德曼先生，
你所作的任何虚假陈述
可用于起诉
伪证罪
你明白吗？
-对。
在过去24小时内，
你习惯了吗
不法官大人。
你要吃什么
不
好吧
持续
哦,嗯,，
呃，我喂了他们一大堆废话
关于她的参与
我只是，我只是想要她
我想让她听到这个。
所以，是的，我不在那里
我不在那里
我没有作证
但我他妈的很清楚
我不止一次
我是不可或缺的。
我让沃尔特保持白色
我洗了他的钱，
我为他撒谎，
我赚了几百万。
如果他没有走的话
沃尔特·怀特
或者在一个月内坐牢。
还有施拉德探员
还有很多其他人
事实上，沃尔特·怀特
你明白了吗？
法官大人，我们要去
基于什么理由？
-嗯，猜测。
他在作证
法官大人，
那会发生的
我还有一件事要说。
-请坐，古德曼先生。现在
政府敦促法院：
允许古德曼先生
这是怎么回事
好的，古德曼先生。
着手
怎么搞的？
这是。。。
我简直无语了。
之后，
金姆有勇气重新开始。
她离开了小镇，但是。。。
我是那个逃跑的人。
还有我弟弟查克--
查尔斯·麦吉尔。
你可能认识他。
他是
最聪明的人
但他是有限的。
我试过了。
我本可以更努力的。
我应该有。
-相反，当--
请给我比尔。
相反，当我看到一个机会
我取消了他的医疗事故保险。
我拿走了
法律。
之后，他自杀了。
我会接受的。
那是什么？
你哥哥的那件事，
是的，是的。
古德曼先生，
我叫麦吉尔。
我是詹姆斯·麦吉尔。
法官大人，
我们想要
-……政府撤回其判刑建议。
-那不是认罪。
施加法定最高限额
那不是认罪。
此外，法官阁下，
…在非常复杂的情况下，
…评估
对不起，麦吉尔先生
你把自己摔倒了吗？
是的，我做到了！
我开始担心了。
我的车在40号公路上抛锚了。
我差一点喝到奶油
哦,嗯,，
他们有那些苹果
我给你买了半打富士牌。
嗯，还有报摊
说他们可能会开始携带
那很好，对吧？
什么
你知道我可以
我可以找个人
我正在做。
是啊，每天？
当你努力的时候
为什么？
因为你是我哥哥。
你也会为我做同样的事。
我们可以谈谈。
说话那么...怎么样
好吧，你的案子。你的客户。
你想谈谈吗
认真地
你想谈谈，
在基督教科学中
那孩子呢
喝了五瓶
然后昏倒了
这是他们应得的
和其他客户一样。
或者你只是想告诉我
那不是我想的。
我希望你没有偷
你可以期待。
我要走了
我的一个“当之无愧”的客户，
他挥舞小玩意被抓住了
等等
这个我请客。
吉米。。。
如果你不喜欢
回去没有什么丢脸的
呃，你什么时候去过
嘿想想看。
我们总是以失败告终
明天见，查克。
而我可能会
我认识你？
“最好叫索尔。”
正当
麦吉尔。
什么
我是麦吉尔。
别给我这个。
你是索尔！
最好打电话给索尔。
没有狗屎。
嘘！嘘！
回到这里，哟。
回到这里。
看见托尔贾！
最好叫索尔！
你说得对。最好打电话给索尔。
你好
是 啊最好打电话给索尔。
-更好。。。
-呼叫。。。
索尔。
-更好。。。
-呼叫。。。
索尔。
最好叫索尔！
-你们都闭嘴！
-最好叫索尔！
最好打电话给。。。
扫罗！律师来了！
我找到你了，索尔。
-夫人？
非常感谢。
嗨，吉米。
你好
你怎么。。。
嗯，原来
不必
你让他们下来了
是的，是的。
八十六年。
但只要行为端正。。。
谁知道呢？
来了，来了。